<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">"Happily Ever After"</string>
    <string name="Button">"NEXT"</string>
    <string name="AA_story1">&quot;Time Out.&quot;</string>
    <string name="AA_story2">&quot;There are certain moments when you should rethink some of life’s decisions.  Maybe you should have kissed that pretty girl when you had a chance.  Or maybe you shouldn’t have volunteered to be the town’s hero.&quot;</string>
    <string name="AA_story3">&quot;As you head toward the Dragon’s lair, you can’t shake the feeling that you might not survive this day.  You think back on your previous accomplishments and remember...&quot;</string>
    <string name="AA_choice1">&quot;You squired for the legendary Sir William the Brave learning the ways of chivalry and how to fight with sword and shield.  Unfortunately, your mentor ended up as Sir William the Breakfast to our local Dragon.&quot;</string>
    <string name="AA_choice2">&quot;You came from little material means, becoming adept at hunting with bow and arrows out of necessity.  You’re surprisingly resourceful, but I wouldn’t say too bright.  After all, you're about to start a fight with a dragon.&quot;</string>
    <string name="AA_choice3">&quot;I don't care.&quot;</string>
    <string name="AB_storyA1">&quot;Hello Knight in shining armor.&quot;</string>
    <string name="AB_storyA2">&quot;You’re the Hero of this story.  You know in your heart that you’re destined for greatness; dragon slaying is going to be only one of many accomplishments.  Some would say it was your trust fund that afforded you to train to heroic strength.  They're just jealous.&quot;</string>
    <string name="AB_storyA3">&quot;Due to your natural skill and talents, you get the following stats:
+50 Strength – Rawrr!  You're so strong you can punch a hole through someone’s chest!&quot;</string>
    <string name="AB_choiceA1">"Answer Choice AB Answer 1"</string>
    <string name="AB_choiceA2">"Answer Choice AB Answer 2"</string>
    <string name="AB_choiceA3">"Answer Choice AB Answer 3"</string>
    <string name="AB_choiceA4">"Answer Choice AB Answer 4"</string>
    <string name="AC_story1">"Story AC Text 1"</string>
    <string name="AC_story2">"Story AC Text 2"</string>
    <string name="AC_story3">"Story AC Text 3"</string>
    <string name="AC_choice1">"Answer Choice AC Answer 1"</string>
    <string name="AC_choice2">"Answer Choice AC Answer 2"</string>
    <string name="AC_choice3">"Answer Choice AC Answer 3"</string>
    <string name="AC_choice4">"Answer Choice AC Answer 4"</string>
    <string name="AD_story1">"Story AD Text 1"</string>
    <string name="AD_story2">"Story AD Text 2"</string>
    <string name="AD_story3">"Story AD Text 3"</string>
    <string name="AD_choice1">"Answer Choice AD Answer 1"</string>
    <string name="AD_choice2">"Answer Choice AD Answer 2"</string>
    <string name="AD_choice3">"Answer Choice AD Answer 3"</string>
    <string name="AD_choice4">"Answer Choice AD Answer 4"</string>
    <string name="AB_choiceB1">&quot; &quot;</string>
    <string name="AB_choiceB2">&quot; &quot;</string>
    <string name="AB_choiceB3">&quot; &quot;</string>
    <string name="AB_storyB1">&quot;Aha!  So you’ve decided to be a Robin Hood hero (though not exactly him because that would be copyright infringement).&quot;</string>
    <string name="AB_storyB2">&quot;Anyways, you’re the Hero of this story. You know better than to engage your enemies in close quarters, especially a Dragon that can take flight at a moment’s notice.&quot;</string>
    <string name="AB_storyB3">&quot;You are stealthy and deadly.  For this, you get the following stats:
+50 Dexterity – You make cats look clumsy.  You can shoot an apple off a person’s head from 500 yards away… most of the time.&quot;</string>
    <string name="AB_storyC1">&quot;Of course you don’t care.  This is a text based choose your own adventure game.  Why would you bother reading through all the answer choices to form a decision?&quot;</string>
    <string name="AB_storyC2">&quot;To be fair, maybe you did read the choices and there just wasn’t anything that caught your eye.  I probably shouldn’t jump to conclusions about people (or at least that’s what my therapist tells me).  No matter!&quot;</string>
    <string name="AB_storyC3">&quot;Here’s some random stats and a random skill.  If anyone asks where you’re from, just mumble and nod.&quot;</string>
    
</resources>